seen them down bad now they trying to
same to hit me for the up early in the
morning it is currently 9:30 in the
morning Vegas time we fell asleep at
6:00 in the morning but I couldn't fall
asleep because we've been simply focused
on one thing and one thing only
streaking Super Bowl boys so we're on
the way right now to the stadium to
study it to see what we can learn what
can we learn so when we go streak we are
successful we have we have a trading
plan to trade so we have a streaking
plan when we
streak
all right so we are trying to scope out
the stadium right now because we're
going to be sneaking in so right now
there's like about four or five cops
looking at us and we're going to try and
play it out like we're like a media team
or some [__] trying to get through so
we're going to see what we can do so
basically we're prend be yeah 100% bro
could do it we can [__] do it right
highest achievement of sneaking in and I
just did it bro so we just kind of have
like a visual representation of what we
have to jump right now so it's about
like 10 ft it's about 10 to 12 feet so
we're going to get a little practice
running cuz this is what we're doing
tomorrow
Gold All right so now he's going to be
the
decoy gold
doin oh you're [__] bro you're [__]
so I know you guys know the goat Vitali
so he hit me up right now he's like yo
what are you doing and then I told him
like yo I'm studying right now to get in
like bro I love it learning from the ogs
I'm a student I'm a student of the
markets you learned from the best n he
is he is good at it bro Pro tip if you
can't beat them go with them so that's
what we're doing right now want right in
right with them all right made it
through security checkpoint one so far
you Advanced nothing you believe in me
we can do it it's not that hard if you
believe in yourself I think becoming a
profit and Tra is harder and you know
that's that's that's we did that so many
people yeah we going against it we we
can't do what the [__] what's that
called the can't follow the crowd you
can't follow the crowd we're doing the
complete opposite of what follow the
crowd we got nowhere you see what
happens when we don't follow the crowd
failed
attempt home so we're going to have to
pay almost like 10K for these tickets
now and then once we go in we'll just
figure it out F the 10 sneak in so no
surprised honestly it's it's the day
before what do you expect we're going to
camp out for [__] two days so it's
official we are going to buy the tickets
right now I don't think you guys
understand how much these tickets are
like I am paying
$30,000 to get
arrested you put it like that we're
[__] idiots cuz it's 15,000 per
ticket look let me show you guys so this
is the stadium right now right this is
the stadium and I have to get as close
as possible to the [__] field so
definitely over here these sections are
a noot because you have the Windfield so
we got to be one of these [__]
right here push these cheerleaders out
the way and then we're on the field baby
you want you want to know why I'm doing
this right now because I got a little
drunk last night and I started talking
so much [__] so when I get drunk I'm I'm
a happy person I just start talking [__]
and I told everybody and their mother
that I was doing this I told Dana I told
Vitaly I told Steve F everybody knows
I'm doing this [__] I'm committing
that's it I got to keep I got to stick
to my word and if I go to jail I go to
jail I'll take a trade before I go in so
when I get out I'm in
profit all right so we just got a sneak
peek of what the Super Bowl is going to
look like right now so that is that
black wall right there is exactly this
section right here so it's 16,000 per
seat so you guys can see right here the
total is 16,000 per seat and I'm going
be honest bro look dude that wall right
there looks higher then the red wall
because if you notice this is the corner
unit and then after the corner one comes
the flat one so that's the corner unit
then comes the first flat one dude that
wall looks [__] taller than the one
that we were practicing in earlier so
it's 16,000 * 2 because [__] set and
forget that's
why cuz we will go down as Legends and
set and forget will go beyond the
financial markets swing trading lab will
be known
as the number one educational company
that has stre a Super Bowl and trust me
we're going to make this legendary all
right let me get your card that's
[__] [__] bro it's 10K in show
them where the [__] are these fees going
to
$40,000 I'm down for 30 but I don't know
if I'm down for 40 dude I L to go to
jail you guys are crazy did you guys
even sleep no we haven't slept again no
dude yo bro we fell asleep at 6 and we
woke up at 8 dude we haven't slept
that's crazy I haven't stopped thinking
about this [__] really yeah that's crazy
all right look so you want to see the
game plan yeah all right so look so this
is this is the stadium right we went
dude there's no way we're sneaking in
that [__] like what do you mean sneaking
in like we were going to sneak in
originally you do the Super Bowl yeah oh
you're [__] out of your mind there's
like 100 thousand ofs there's no zero
chance zero that should not
happen that's
it holy [__] bro holy [__] oh your car
was already in there you were waiting
that's crazy bro you're [__] insane
bro yeah I can't put a story on that
they're going to think I'm coming and
they're going to go and [__] press
you on those seats congrats bro write
write me on a piece of paper your full
legal name so I can be calling Bail
Bonds there
there what the [__] did
do yeah just swiped so fast ax you
didn't even
come
[__] we are legends all right brother we
are [__] Legends s and forget s and
[__]
forget all right so we are 7 hours away
from the Super
Bowl my heart is [__] pounding we
going to make some vets real quick got
about 50,000 so it's just 100,000 in
like 24 hours 50,000 in Super Bowl
tickets and then we're about to bet the
rest of it right now 7 hours away I'm
nervous I'm actually nervous I'm
actually nervous bro nervous about what
it's not like we're going to go spend
the night in jail that's not that bad
let's be honest that's not all right
we're going to go hit the gym a little
warm
up stretching we got to we got to
practice our
Jukes I'm
actually we got we got our bets in so
some nice cute little bets so we pretty
much had to max out on a prop bet so
202,000 2500 2800 I go to about like 50k
but the only that is
10K
what are you trying to warm up
for I got what is that going to help
with hit him with the hit him with
the practice my
barrels why we need
practice you're definitely caught are
you actually doing this yes bro holy
[__] this it's the most washed Super
Bowl figure out a bad thing or no says
uh he hasn't been able to find it bro
but if you can bro like I'm I'm doing it
dude I'm I'm I'm in to deep Bro already
so I it's going down if you can if you
can find that line bro I I'll put up
money too tell Vince to start looking
tell Vince everyone in the house start
googling it right now it's going to it's
going to be somewhere on one of these
sites I'm on my way right now to buy the
shoes then I just go straight to the
Super Bowl so if you were to
hypothetically have to run onto the
field right and hypothetically not get
noticed you're wearing fats noted like
like people can't notice when wearings
which ones would you pick what sport
it's a football field you're looking for
something low key this going to be the
best option for sure it's a little bit
higher key like a little bit little bit
more but I'm not going to lie those look
good huh the goat himself is wearing
these might be it dude Crazy Fast yeah
oh it's a wrap yeah we'll take we'll
take
these not suspicious at all no warming
up that doesn't feel good though yeah it
does you do that [__] terrible feel like
high
school yeah you're in deep already
you're inom all right so I Gotto but I
got to geted up we're going to do FX
Alex G here right FX don't get my and
then right here # s forget and then
we'll do s forget right here in the back
already [__] up wait did you yeah it's
going be too small I mean it's going to
be
greetings just do your thing bro I
just hey look you didn't see nothing
right you got to run on thei tonight
today or what what are you talking
about what kind of ad is that bro why
are you guys doing this in the bathroom
bro not on the [__] bed laying
down any any words of inspiration
run just
run instead of forget thank you guys
good luck see you guys see you on the
other
side wa you want is right here we going
to give them what they came for we going
to take it up from last year shoot them
my shot Bo I'm long range me and the
team on the same thing down never
switched off only thing changed was the
game I'm in the zone now
[Music]
all right so we still out the place
right now this has so many security
[Music]
guard Ms keeping the play alive for
seemingly hours now this offense has
changed so much over the years so every
single one of us guys wearing a yellow
jacket is a security guard we have a
we're going to keep thinking about it
[Music]
but who running the game now foot on the
gas can slow down my team weing yo what
team you going for dolphins I'm going
for the red team the red team yeah who's
the red team they're both red
ra we know we running it now watch the
game change
watch the
game
theame theame we aren't supposed to be
here for Hal time but whatever we're
going to get the 14k worth of tickets
right now it's some entertainment yo any
last R oh we got people on the field oh
my goodness we do we got a Streaker on
the other well here's a partial Streaker
partial Streaker
no but we can't talk about
it holy [__]
oh oh no
oh oh there's
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
two that is the stupidest [__] we've
ever done bro was it worth
it about to find out
yo who shirt is that why you wearing my
shirt is that I don't know